if your videos do not exceed 200 views
these are three mistakes you are making without realizing it
question for entrepreneurs start-up with malta
what is the quality
in common in this house that is full of digital entrepreneurs.
I want them to share that it is precisely the
reason what is its success
half massive the question yes very massive but bank
the question bank the question bank the question
are all
as people with achieving something and that's what you look at are the
10 and 42 p.m.
and
we are working
it is as if we live a very good life,
very quiet.
but an urgency and as if the world was going to go away
and is a priority
I am an agency that is mainly dedicated to looking at texts.
yes
no but tell me what you are doing Juan
an agency dedicated to
to generate prospects for real estate developers and real estate agents
and nothing we basically uninstall the attention
permission system from its content
and automations so that all they do is accelerate these situations.
very well that's right compa let's go with another question vos mate
in these 5 days that he came with entrepreneurs
what was something in particular that surprised you that you had seen
em I like it I really like to see how the others do eh
and the way they work on a day-to-day basis and
to the level of urgency as they were just saying from
eh every day we wake up calmly
we make a mate whatever and then pah pah pah that we have to do things.
and we don't stop and we go for a walk we go to the gym we come back we continue
we are preparing an asado,
we are still talking about things
the truth is that something very very and something
concrete is generated from an episode.
punctual eh an anecdote
listen to Facu yesterday farting at 7 ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha hey
friend I asked for a stupid sermon
he was anal priest where he told you hey put eggs ha ha ha
son of a bitch
Instagram fell down eh no no but there is no message ha ha ha ha ha ha
ja the calendar was broken
as far as you know they are not going to shit payment no
give it something specific,
so you have it left.
well, yes,
a concrete anecdote,
a concrete anecdote.
what to say I like this if I like it
peace,
and calm with the cup,
the creator of
Mateo mafia content that another thing that surprised me was
the ability to take videos from out of nowhere you understand
I arrived at the hotel I'm next to the bag I
went to eat something the bag and the guy
I had three videos loaded my friend
and uploaded 6 TikToks you understand
and you didn't see it recording no and that's that's
is number one but peace
look at him look at him look at him calmly he is a gentleman he has a company
Mount Mount that's having a company,
not the pastor.
is the shepherd even the necklaces looks like a monk man
in other words,
there is nothing that can alter it.
is solved
and if you see the longest TikTok you are going to upload,
it is spectacular.
episode number one in the house of culture as is
if you are here watching it
you're a jerk,
how many viewers do you have on TikTok,
you're a
you are a real you are a real
number one anichás in your cu
no one cares
strategy for real estate agents who want to sell through TikTok as he did.
Rafa selling $1 million in property
I know you something well I am doing
well bye